Curriculum Vitae

Personal

Name Brian Teddy Omondi

Address Nairobi

Phone number **0715551892**

Email teddybrian543@gmail.com

Gender Male

Nationality Kenyan

Driving licence B

LinkedIn https://bit.ly/3p3hs9p

Resume objective

I am an software developer and a graphic designer who has completed his studies at Strathmore University. I have worked in the IT department as an assistant and I have been able to interact with a lot both in the IT sector and work environment.

Work experience

Jan 2020 - Mar 2020

Support Staff

Muhuri Muchiri, Nairobi

Worked as a Physical Education teacher for the students at Muhuri Muchiri Secondary, where I also engaged as an assistant coach for the school's rugby team.

Worked with the administration as an IT support and took part in registering students into the school NEMIS system, digitizing of notes and making repairs for IT related problems.

Feb 2021 - Mar 2021

IT Assistant

Keysian Auctioneers Debt Collection and Recovery, Nairobi

Worked in the IT department of the debt collection firm as an IT Assistant. Was responsible of being the IT support where I fixed any errors that would arise from the users. My responsibilities also included server administration and network maintenance. I registered new users into the company's system and enrolled them into the telephony services.

Education and Qualifications

Jul 2018 - Jan 2022

Bachelor of Science Informatics and Computer Science

Strathmore University, Nairobi

Studied for my University degree in Bachelor of Science in Informatics and Computer Science.

Feb 2014 - Nov 2017

K.C.S.E

Lenana School, Nairobi

Studied for my high school education at Lenana where I finished with a mean grade of B+ in the K.C.S.E.

Nov 2013

K.C.P.E

Fadhili Junior School, Nairobi

Took my primary education where I finished with a mean of 419 in K.C.P.E

Interests

Creative Writing, Art and Design, Game development, ,

References

Keysian Auctioneers

Lucas Okewe

0719559334

lokewe@keysian.co.ke

Muhuri Muchiri Secondary School Peter Makundi 0722289698

Skills

UI/UX Design ● ● ● ●

Microsoft packages ● ● ● ●

Computer Networking • • • • •

Server Administration • • • • •

Coding • • • • •